Are you okay with that?
I'm here to debate you, not debate them.
I mean, you're all on the same side.
You're part of one group.
No.
You've been clapping each other.
No, I mean, there are conservatives here.
There are far right people here.
There are Republicans here.
But how do you feel about that guy
wanting me and you to leave?
But, you know, let's stick-
I'm just wondering.
This is the topic of immigration.
It's not about my- How do you feel about the guy?
It's not about my feelings towards them.
Okay.
It's about staying on this topic.
And talk about- Immigrants are good for America, yeah.
You and me, we're good for America.
And the guy over there wants us to leave.
So I'm just wondering how you feel about that.
So I believe that there has to be
strict immigration laws.
Okay.
We have to make sure that the people are coming here
have the good intent of the United States in mind.
That's not my claim, but okay.
So-
My claim is about immigrants are net positive.
If you just open our borders to every single person
that wants to be here- No one calls for open borders.
You know, that claims that they have
economical hardship in their country.
Who's calling for open borders?
I'm just saying, you know-
Oh, I mean, it's a straw man.
So you're just saying a straw man.
No, I'm saying that if-
You're wasting time with a straw man.
No one's calling for open borders.
I didn't call for open borders.
Well, you wasted time-
You wasted time trying to cause division
between me and my friend over here.
Division?
He wants you to leave the country.
That's a pretty big deal.